Amanda Steele Show. Today's Figo Figo goes to actor Trevante Rhodes' back in the sex scene
of the new movie Mea Culpa. The movie, the movie is getting, um, you know, Tyler Perry-esque
reviews, okay? Uh, some people have called it even soft porn, like, kind of like, remember
Skinamax? Remember those movies that would come on? Yes, I do. Back to Trevante's back,
there is a scene with a lot of paint involved and a lot of just, you know, um, waist movements
involved, but it really took me back to DMX in Belly, and if you understand that reference,
then you know that it's going to be worth your time to go and check out this reference, okay?
Today's lockdown goes to the not-so-friendly skies. Passengers aboard a Delta flight from Amsterdam to
Detroit got a disgusting surprise when maggots were found falling from a carry-on bag that
was stored in an overhead bin. Apparently, there was, like, rotten fish in the bag, and the maggots
fell out of the bag onto a woman in the seat below. I don't think you understand. They would have had
to do the overhead, you know, when they come on, like, is there, is there any physicians? Do we have
any physicians on the plane? Like, that would have been the next thing that the flight attendant would
have had to do because I would have gone into cardiac arrest. Careful on these planes, y'all. I may have
to put that hazmat suit back on that we was wearing in the panini.